所以你不介意我割断最后一根绳子吧？
So you're okay with me cutting the final rope?
老天爷啊
Oh my god.
我们要剪最后一根绳子！
We're cutting the final rope!
三 二 一 剪！
Three, two, one, cut!
这可能相当于获得了$100万美元
This could equal a million dollars.
感觉如何？
How's it feel?
有点吓人
It's kind of scary.
欢迎来到二号位（选手）
And welcome to the number two slot.
现在感觉如何？
How do you feel?
很好 我准备好赢了
I'm good, I'm ready to win.
这比你想象的容易还是困难？
Is this easy or harder than you thought it would be?
我不会说 因为你们会让它变得更难
I'm not gonna say, cause y'all are gonna make it harder.
你感觉如何？
How do you feel?
老实说 吓尿了 我对高空有极大的恐惧
Freaking out, not gonna lie. I have huge fear of heights.
你们中最后一个掉进这水里的人 将得到竞争$100万美元的机会
Last one of you guys to fall into this pool of water, gets the chance at one million dollars.
不会吧！！
No way!
我的意思是这样的
And here's what I mean by that.
我们将有四个“最后离开挑战”的视频
We are going four last to leave videos
每一个挑战的获胜者将在第五个视频中竞争$100万美元
and the winners of each will compete in a fifth video for one million dollars.
你现在正在观看本系列的第一部分
You are currently watching part one of this series.
我不在乎谁赢了 但不管谁赢了
I don't care who wins, but whoever does,
都会在几周后飞回来与其他赢家争夺$100万美元
will fly back in a few weeks and compete against the other winners for a million dollars.
这可以说是我们做过的最极端的挑战
This is arguably the most extreme thing we've ever done.
看到这个笼子了吗？
See this cage?
我们从美国武士忍者（American Warrior Ninja）弄来的 就那个
We took it from American Warrior Ninja, that thing.
我们放了一些绳子 还放了一些人在上面
We put some ropes and we put some people on it.
我们又拿了$100万美元 这就是为啥我们出现在这里
And we grabbed a million dollars and that's how we ended up here.
就像我说的 克里斯（Chris） 我们要做四个“最后离开挑战” 这是第一个
So as I said Chris, we're doing four last to leaves, this is the first one.
而前四个挑战的获胜者将在第五个视频中参与争夺$100万美元的奖金
And the winners of all four compete in a fifth one for one million dollars.
也就是说还有三个“最后离开挑战”视频
Which means there's three more.
那你要怎么挑选其他竞争人员？
So how you gonna pick all the other people?
很高兴你问了
I'm glad you asked.
这是如何
Here's how.
如果你买了商品 或者在照片墙（Instagram）上关注我 你就会被邀请 就是这么简单
If you buy merch, or follow me on Instagram, you'll be entered. It's that simple.
我们会随机挑选在照片墙上关注我的人
We're gonna randomly pick people who follow me on Instagram
或者从现在到接下来的几次挑战中购买商品的人
or people who buy merch in between now and the next few challenges
我们将邀请他们参加比赛
and we're gonna invite'em down to compete.
我会在视频结尾提醒你们
And I'll remind you about that at the end of the video.
我们会给你们每个人一个教练
So we gave each of you guys a coach
让他们每组穿同样的衬衫 这样观众就能分辨
and we made them wear the same shirt so the viewers could tell.
卡梅伦（Cameron） 你的教练是克里斯
Cameron, your coach is Chris.
阿尔贝托（Alberto） 你有马库斯（Marcus）
Alberto you have Marcus.
科尔比（Colby） 我们给你个钱德勒（Chandler）所以如果你想的话 现在就可以退出了
Colby, we brought you a Chandler, so you can just go ahead and just get out now if you want to.
不！不要这么说！
No! Don't say that!
还有你被分配到大个子维京
And you are assigned the big guy.
好了 你们每个人都有一个教练 他们会给你提供任何你需要的
So there you go, you each have a coach, they'll get you whatever you need.
最后一个倒下的人可以继续前进并争取$100万奖金 祝你们好运
Whoever falls last gets to move on and compete for one million dollars, good luck.
我想看看你在上面能不能给你弄瓶水 我们来试一试
I want to see if I can get you a bottle of water like up there, let's give it a shot.
-科比！ -啊！
-Kobe! -Ah, oh!
卡梅伦 这和你的衬衫很搭
Cameron, this matches your shirt.
哦 好接球！
Oh good catch!
给你来一根香蕉
A banana for you.
-给你的香蕉！ -等一下 等一下
-A banana for you! -Wait, wait, wait.
哇！他甚至都没有动！
Whoa! He didn't even move!
呃 额 呃 额 呃 额 呃 额
Uh, huh, uh, huh, huh, uh, huh.
克里斯 我们即将迎来我们的第一个挑战
So Chris, we're gonna do our first challenge.
在你们身后都有座位 你们可以争取坐着休息的时间来助自己取胜
There's seats behind you and you can earn time for sitting to help you win.
这个挑战的奖励是可以坐上休息一分钟 你得把这个鸡蛋扔给你的选手
The first challenge for one minute of sitting, you have to throw your contestant this egg,
他必须将其扔回去 并且没有裂痕 如果能完成 他就可以坐下一分钟
and he has to toss it back, without a crack. And if you do that, he can sit.
-老兄 我从来就不擅长运动 -低手球
-Dude, I was never good at sports. -underhand.
很好
All right.
失误！
Bloop!
来吧 马库斯
All right, Marcus.
哦 我的上帝
Oh my God.
给你的鸡蛋
Here's an egg.
-好球！ -如果钱德勒抓到了你就可以坐下来
-Great shot! -And if Chandler catches this you get to sit.
唔 这就对了！
Ooh there we go!
没有裂缝
And no cracks.
因此 既然他们完成了鸡蛋挑战 她就得到一点坐下休息的时间
So since they completed the egg challenge, she gets a little bit of sitting time.
给你的座位
There's your seat.
科尔比获得一分钟坐下的奖励
Colby gets to sit for the next minute.
恭喜！
Congrats!
你在帮助你的参赛手
You're helping your contestant.
在科尔比把时间快用光的时候 让我们看看你能不能给他争取一些
While Colby's wrapping up her sitting time, let's see if you can earn him some.
完美！
Perfect!
啊！
Ah!
完好无损
It is perfect.
我会把座位放下来
I will lower the seat.
科尔比 你的时间到了 起身 不要跌倒
So, Colby, your minute is up, stand up. Try not to fall.
现在我们收回她的座位
And now we will take her seat back.
杰克（Jake）的选手想要一些休息时间 所以我们给他一个椅子
And Jake's contestant wants some sitting time, so we give him his seat
在你身后来了！
Coming down behind ya!
好了 欢呼！
There it is, yeah!
最后一条 如果你的选手赢了 他们将继续争夺$100万美元
One final thing, if your contestant wins, they go on to compete for a million dollars.
为了激励大家帮助各自的玩家获胜
To incentivize you guys to help your players win,
如果他们赢得$100万美元 他们必须给你10％
if they win the million dollars, they have to give you 10%.
-喔 你最好给我赢 -给你们一点激励
-Ooh, you better win. -To incentivize you guys.
你需要什么我都给你
I'll get you anything you need.
那是$10万大奖 而他们仍然还有$90万大奖
That's $100 grand, and they still win $900 grand.
现在你们也要承担风险
Now that you guys also have money on the line,
让我们再做一次鸡蛋挑战 但要从更远的地方开始 这次奖励五分钟而不是一分钟
let's do the egg challenge again, but from further back. This time it's for five minutes instead of one.
不要越过这个 我们的奖金是$100万美金 而我们的标记是一袋薯片
Don't cross that, we have a million dollars on the line and our markers a bag of chips.
这次只需要接住就行了 他就可以坐五分钟
This time we'll just do if he catches it. He can sit for five minutes.
-唉！ -做的好！
-Aw! -It's good!
-是不是从他两腿之间跑过去了？ -是的
-Did that go between his legs? -Yeah it did.
-不会的 -不可能
-Not it. -Nope.
哦！
Oh!
五分钟 我会降低椅子
That's five minutes. I'll go lower it.
你的奖励 科尔比
Here you go Colby.
我打赌他接不住的
I bet he's not gonna catch it.
哦 不！
Oh no!
这算吗?
Does that count?
天啊！
Oh my gosh!
体育 非我所长也
Sports, not good at 'em.
那现在谁认为自己领先一点？
So who thinks they're in first place right now?
老实说 我的意思就是我了
I mean, honestly, right here.
-你认为你是第一？-是的
-You think you're first place? -yeah
那是什么？
Who's that?
那是蓄意破坏 你必须绕着池子游十圈
That was sabotage. You have to do ten laps around the pool.
你不能把东西扔向竞争对手！
You can't throw things at the competitors!
我能做我想做的！
I can do what I want!
当我闻到有人蓄意破坏时 灯光会变红 警报就会响起
When I smell sabotage, the lights turn red and the alarm comes out.
哦 这会很冷的
Oh this is gonna be cold.
阿克 好冷！
Ack, it's so cold!
好了 这是一圈
Well there we go, that's one lap.
这就是破坏者的下场
This is what happens to sabotagers here.
我好冷啊！
I'm cold!
越来越难了
Its getting a bit more difficult.
现在是我们第一个激励的时间了
Now it's time for our first incentive.
这是一只礼物独角兽
This is the unicorn of gifts.
第一个退出的人 可以拥有iPhone Airpods Beats和PS4
First person to get out, can have an iPhone, Airpods, Beats, and PS4.
想想吧 我不在乎是谁
Just consider it, I don't care who it is.
没人嘛 真的吗？
Nobody, really?
没有人想要独角兽的爱吗？
No one wants the unicorn of love?
很好 他们很固执 谁给我一把刀
All right, they're being stubborn, someone give me a knife.
等等 什么刀？
Wait a minute, what?
事情有一段时间了 红灯起
Things are lasting a while, red light me.
哦 来了！
Ooh there we go!
我们要剪短这个绳子
We'll just cut this rope.
-嘿 不要割绳子！ -哇 哇 哇 哇！
-Hey, don't cut the rope! -Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
-不 不 -哦
-No, no -Ooh.
他们只剩下16根绳子了
They're down to 16 ropes.
-哦 你还要来 哦 -十五根！
-Oh you're going again, oh.-Fifteen.
20根绳索中有5根没了 感觉如何？
Five of those twenty ropes are gone, how does it feel?
-感觉很不一样 -我不信你 我要剪掉更多
-There's a big difference but -I don't believe you, I'm cutting more.
好了 把灯调回正常 我们没事了
All right, turn the lights back to normal, we're good.
再试一次
Try again.
你差点把他淘汰掉！
You almost got him out!
我的锅！
My bad!
你们有十分钟的时间来画一幅参赛者的画像
You guys have ten minutes to draw a portrait of your contestant.
然后我会让我社交媒体上的人投票选出最好的一个 观众将决定
I will then let people on my social media vote with a poll for the best one. The viewers will decide.
无论他们投给谁 都可以坐下十分钟
Whoever they vote, gets ten minutes of sitting down.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
你知道钱德勒（大沙雕） 我不能说让我印象深刻
You know Chandler, I can't say I'm impressed.
你看不出来这是什么吗？ 看起来和她在做的一模一样 是吧？
You can't tell what that is though? It looks exactly like what she's doing, right?
克里斯 看起来很不错
Oh Chris that looks good.
植树 照亮你的美
Trees are lit.
好吧 你准备好了吗？
All right, you ready for this?
哦 其实没那么糟
Oh, that's actually not that bad.
准备好欣赏这幅杰作吧 孩子
Get ready for this masterpiece son.
你喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
-我喜欢 -看明白了吧？
-I love it. -You see it, right?
恩 懂了 吗？
Uh, yeah, no?
不？
No?
你准备好了吗？
Are you ready for this?
太棒了 我喜欢上面废柴的标记
That is awesome I like the loser signs on it.
我包含了一切 所以我认为这个是赢家 是吧？
I drew everything. So I think this is a winner, you know?
准备好迎接美丽了吗？
Are you ready for the beautiful?
我花了（桃）绒毛和所有的
I got the peach fuzz and everything,
他的胸口有W 你想知道为什么吗？
it's got a W on your chest, you wanna know why?
冬季（赢家）
Winter（winner）.
所以我在社交媒体上做了一个调查
So I put a poll out on social media,
顺便说一句 如果你想来这里参加下一场比赛 请关注我的照片墙
which by the way, follow my Instagram if you wanna potentially be here, next competition.
但是不管怎样 我让你们投票 你们选择杰克就是赢家
But regardless, I let you guys vote. And you guys decided that Jake is the winner.
-什么？ -什么？
-What? -What?
对
Yup.
赢家赢得了狗屁 克里斯才是真的赢家！
The winner of nothing, Chris actually won!
欢呼！
Yeah!
好难过
So sad.
它不起作用
It didn't work.
-哦 感觉怎么样 小老弟 -感觉爽歪歪！
-Oh how does that feel man? -It feels amazing!
看看他 他全身都在躺着！你们几位肯定贼羡慕吧
Look at him, he's laying all the way back! You guys are jelly right now.
情况已变得非常艰难 所以我想让你给家人打电话 试着获得一些动力
It's been getting pretty tough, so I want you to call a family member and try to get some motivation.
嘿 怎么样了？你弟弟和另外四个人被吊在泳池上
Hey, how's it going? Your brother is suspended above a pool, and there's four other people,
谁最后下来的人谁就有机会赢得$100万美元
whoever gets out last gets to compete for a million dollars.
天啊
Oh my gosh.
嘿 妈妈 我没告诉你 因为你可能会对我发脾气
Hey mom, so I didn't tell you, 'cause you'd go off on me probably.
你为什么不用你的手机打电话？
Why aren't you calling from your cell phone?
妈妈 这是竞赛 我不能有电话 我正在争夺$100万美元
Mom, it's a competition, I can't have my phone. I'm competing to win a million dollars.
她在说 天哪 你是认真的？
She's saying oh my God are you serious.
嘿 咋样了 老爸？
Hey what's up dad?
如果我赢了这场比赛 那么我会在十二月回去 有机会赢得100万美元
If I win this one, then I go back in December and have a chance to win a million dollars.
你什么？
You what?
真不错 孩子
That's great man.
好的 选手们 财富的独角兽又回来了
All right contestants, the unicorn of wealth is coming back.
不管谁下一个退出 我们都有Beats耳机 Airpods iPhone XboxOne PS4
For whoever gets out next, we have some Beats, some Airpods, an iPhone, an Xbox 1, a PS4,
这是之前的情况 现在我们又添了一台MacBookPro 和一些PS4视频游戏
that's what was up there earlier. And now, we're adding in a MacBook Pro. And some PS4 video games.
你所要做的就是现在退出 然后就可以拥有它们
All you have to do is get out now and you can have 'em.
即使你今天在这里赢了 也不能保证你赢了$100万美元
Even if you win here today, you're not guaranteed a million dollars.
这是很多东西 大约$3千5百美元
That's a lot of stuff though. It's about $3,500 dollars.
来做吧 来个人
Go ahead and do it, somebody do it.
这个时候要是小钱钱就退出了
See right about now is when Chandler would get out.
-实际上不会 早着呢 -是的 早早着呢
-Actually way earlier. -Yeah, way earlier.
我只想说那有很多好东西 就是说 如果有这些也挺好
No I'm just sayin' like that's a lot of stuff man, like you know, if you go along way with that
-$100万美元也很好 -我知道
-So is a million dollars. -I know.
他正在考虑
He's considering it.
-做吧 做吧！ -你现在得跳了！
-Do it, do it! -You gotta jump now!
你（独角兽）正在实现自己的命运
You're fulfilling your destiny.
欢欢欢呼呼呼呼！
Yeah!
噢噢噢噢噢噢 太冷了！
No, that's so cold!
-哦！ -不 太冷了！
-Oh! -No, that's so cold!
你妈妈现在会对你说什么？
What would your mother say to you right now?
天哪 他放弃了$100万美元！
Oh my God he gave up a million dollars!
他放弃了$90万 也放弃了你的$10万
He gave up 900 bands and gave up your hundred.
我们还有三次这样的机会 你还会在其中担任教练 所以你还有其他机会
We have three more of these, where you'll also be a coach and so you still have other chances.
在照片墙上关注我或者购买商品 你可能就有机会
Follow me on Instagram or buy merch, you could have a chance.
-这是你的所有物品 -告诉我在上面的时候感受如何？
-So here's all your items. -Tell me how you were feeling when you were up there.
我已经很痛苦了 但不再呆在上面真的感觉很好
I was already in pain, it feels good not to be up there anymore though.
-是的 -没开玩笑
-Yeah. -It's no joke.
你在那里呆了13个小时
You were up there for 13 hours.
13个小时 老兄！
13 hours, man!
-好的 谢谢你能来 非常感谢 我希望你玩得开心 -是的
-Well, thanks for coming, appreciate it.  -Yeah.
阿尔贝托 你做得很好 兄弟
Alberto, you did a good job, bro.
现在只有你们三个人了 你有什么感觉？
So there's only three of you now. How does that make you feel?
我觉得很兴奋 是的 我觉得很乐观
I feel hyped, yeah, I feel optimistic.
科尔比 他走了你有什么感觉？
Colby, how do you feel now that he's gone?
我准备好了 我兴奋极了
I'm ready, I'm hyped.
卡梅伦 你怎么样？
How about you Cameron?
我觉得不挤了 能让我做点想做的 现在我更有信心了
I feel like I got more space to kind of just do what I want and I feel more confident now.
你们其中的一个有机会赢得$100万美元 另外两个将什么都没有 祝你们好运
One of you will get the chance at winning a million dollars, the other two, nothing, so, good luck.
她正在移动到隔壁的间隙
She's moving over to close the gap.
为了纪念阿尔贝托的离开 我们应该剪一条绳子
In honor of Alberto's exit, we should cut a rope.
你说得对
You're right actually.
为了纪念他的退出
In honor of his exit.
红灯
Red lights.
我们开始有20根绳子 现在只剩15根了
We started with twenty ropes, we're down to 15.
现在我们要剪了 所以现在剩下14个了
I think we'll just do this. So now we're down to 14.
现在我们剩下 13根
Now we're just gonna, 13.
-我让你们投票 要不要再剪一个？-不要
-I'll let you guys vote, should I cut one more? -No.
-你觉得呢？阿基拉（Akira）？ -要
-What do you think Akira?  -Yeah
-科尔比 你的想法？ -我意思 很明显（要）
-Colby what do you think? -I mean, obviously
好的 两个同意
Okay, that's two yeses.
哇 他们想结束掉这一切
Whoa, they wanna get this over with.
如果我再剪一个 那就是12个
If I cut another, that puts us at 12.
-哇 -我们在损失绳子
-Wow. -We're droppin' ropes.
-十二个 -哇
-Twelve it is. -Wow.
你们没什么东西可以站了
You guys are running out of things to stand on.
灯光恢复 我们稍后再剪断一些绳子
Lights back to normal, we'll cut some more ropes later.
开玩笑的 重新打开红灯
Just kidding, turn the red lights back on.
天哪 吉米（唐纳森）不跟他们玩了！
Oh my God. Jimmy (Donaldson)'s not playing with them!
那只是个玩笑 灯光正常
Sike! that was justa joke, normal lights.
在这里呆几个小时了？
How many hours have been up here?
克里茜 醒醒 醒醒 杰茜 醒醒 醒醒
Chrissy, wakie, wakie. Jakie, wakie, wakie.
为什么他的头上有一根薯条？
Why is there a french fry on his head?
你们三个每人还有一位选手 你想对卡梅伦说什么？
Each of you three still have a contestant left. What do you want to say to Cameron?
他知道自己是一个野兽和战士
He knows he's a beast and a warrior.
你想说什么？
What do you want to say?
你做的很棒
You're doing amazing.
你呢？酷
You? Awesome,
如果有人在下一分钟内退出 我给他$5千美元
if someone gets out within the next minute, I'll give them $5,000 dollars.
他真是个野兽和勇士
He know she's a beast and a warrior.
你就喜欢幸灾乐祸
You love to see it.
这就是你现在醒着的原因
That's what you wake up to today.
我尽力了 我在上面干了很长时间
I tried man, I was dying for a long time up there.
你本可以轻松点的 伙计
You could've had it easy man.
他看起来很强壮
He looks like he's going pretty strong.
你打算拿这$5千美元做什么？
What are you going to do with that $5,000?
我要捐一些树 也许去买些商品
I'm gonna donate some trees, maybe go do some shopping.
他已经尽其所能了
He tried his best,
嘿 至少他没有空手回家 可怜的科尔比要两手空空了
hey, at least he didn't go home empty handed. Poor Colby's gonna go home empty handed.
剩下你的选手和你的
Your contestant and your contestant remain.
是的
Yeah.
现在卡梅伦走了 剩你们两个争夺$100万美元的机会
Now that Cameron is gone, it is you two fighting for a chance at one million dollars.
哇！
Whoo!
我们先从科尔比开始 卡梅伦走了 ​​你感觉如何？
So we'll start off with you Colby. Cameron's gone, how you feeling?
我感到更加自信 我在这里赢得那$100万
I'm feeling even more confident. I'm here to win that million.
你呢 现在情况如何？
How 'bout you, how are things going now?
-48
-48.
-他要坚持48个小时？ -48 冲啊！
-He's lasted 48 hours? -48, let's go!
好的 当你感到劳累的时候 要想想$100万是很多的
Okay, whenever you get tired remember, a million dollars is a lot
如果你输掉比赛 你的哥哥将会很难过的 好的玩得开心
and your brother would be really sad if you didn't win it. Okay have fun.
所以钱德勒不得不离开 因此我们将交由你负责科尔比
So Chandler had to leave, so we're gonna put you in charge of Colby.
嘘
Boo.
下一分钟 如果有人退出 就会得到$1万美元 然后就会减为$7千
For the next minute, it'll be ten grand if someone gets out, then it drops back to seven.
你可不止这样 阿基拉
You can do better Akira.
你有55秒的时间来决定 然后它回落到$7千美元
You have 55 seconds to decide, and then it falls back to seven grand.
他们有点过了 但那算是很多钱
That's pushing it, that's a lot.
你有40秒的时间赢$1万美金
You have 40 seconds to win ten grand.
你可能在$100万美元的回合中输掉并一无所获
You could just lose in the million dollar round and get nothing,
而此时此刻 你可以带着一万美元离开
when right now, you could walk away with ten grand.
$1万美金 我们等着就是这个
Ten grand, we were waiting on this.
阿基拉 你可以拿那$1万和你的双胞胎哥哥平分 他会很开心的
Akira, you could take that 10K and split it with your twin he's be happy with you.
或者你可以为这$100万继续 并有可能赢得$100万美元
Or you can play for this million and potentially win a million dollars.
但我们加入就是要赢得
But we're in it to win it.
是的！
Yeah!
五 四 三 二 我们来这就是来赢得
Five, four, three, two We came to win,
是的 阿基拉！我们来赢了！
that's right Akira! We came to win!
这是一个非常疲惫但坚定的人
That is a very tired but determined man.
我喜欢 阿基拉
I love that Akira.
现在还剩$7千 随时都可以拿走
Seven grand's still on the table, take it whenever.
剪绳时间！
Rope cutting time.
一旦我开始割绳子 你们其中一个就会掉下去
Once I start cutting some ropes, one of you are gonna fall.
-开始了！ -一根已断
-Here we go! -One down.
两根
That's two.
三根已断
Three down.
阿基拉 你说的算 还要继续吗？
Akira, make the call, you want one more?
是的 继续吧
Yeah, do it.
嘿！
Hey!
我不知道你踩了多少 但不多
I don't know how many you're hanging on, but it's not many.
好吧 祝你好运！
All right, good luck!
给你 跟着我
Here you go, follow me.
我们要走多远？
How far back we going?
我们要出去吗？
Are we going out here?
如果他没抓住 我就再剪断一根绳子
If he doesn't catch it, I cut another rope.
你要接住它 准备好了吗?
You gotta catch it, you ready?
当然 为什么不呢？
Yeah sure, why not?
走起
yeet
差一点
So close.
小马库 钱德勒不见了 所以你来负责 给你
Marky Mark, Chandler disappeared, so, you're in charge. Here you go.
好了 你准备好了吗？科尔比
All right you ready Colby?
就这里 朝着我
Right here, at me.
哦！
Oh!
两根要断
Two ropes it is.
天哪 两根！
Oh my God, two ropes!
红灯起！
Red light me!
开始了
Here we go.
一 二 三 四 五 六根绳子
One, two, three, four, five, six ropes.
哦 现在我们去另一边
Oh, now let's go to the other side.
刀给我
Knife me.
现在有四根绳子了 我们应该在每边再剪一根 让它结束掉吗？
Now there's four ropes, should we just do one more on each side and just get it done with?
阿基拉 你同意吗？
Akira, do you agree?
-是的 -好的
-Yeah. -Okay.
现在剩下三根绳子了
There are now three ropes remaining.
赢得$7千 但你得跳进泳池
Win $7,000. You know you gotta jump in the pool.
你们就是不肯让步
You guys just don't budge.
你想让我做什么 把它剪成一根绳子?
What do you want me to do, just cut it down to one rope?
-来吧 剪 -剪？
-Let's do it. -Let's do it?
是的
Yeah.
让我们问问我们的顾问 卡梅伦
Let's ask our consultant, Cameron.
你在上面过 你知道他们的感受 我们应该剪的只剩下一根绳子吗？
You were up there, you know how they feel, should we go down to one rope?
他们已经在那里待了很长时间 所以我说是的
They've been up there quite some time so I say yeah.
别再说了 一根走起
Say no more, one rope.
红灯
Red lights.
剩下三根绳子
Three ropes remain.
我知道你现在感觉有所不同
I know you feel a difference now.
-你们都觉得吗？ -是的
-Y'all feelin' that? -Yeah.
好的 到另一边
Okay, to the other side.
还是$1万美元 有人想要吗？
Still ten grand, anyone want it?
我想结束你的痛苦 所以我们在那里剪了一个
I'm trying to end your suffering so we cut one over there.
只剩一根
One rope remains.
正式只剩下一根绳子了 我们可以割断最后一根绳子 然后最后一个落水的获胜
There's officially one rope left. We could cut the last rope and do last fall into water.
决胜之战
It'll be a shootout.
但是如果你们都同意的话我才会这么做
But I'd only do it if you both agreed to it.
你想做吗？科尔比
You wanna do it Colby?
好 我们还是结束吧
Well we might as well get it over with.
所以我可以剪掉最后一根绳子吗？
So you're okay with me cutting the final rope?
-哦 我的上帝！ -我们要剪最后的绳子！
-Oh my God! -We're cutting the final rope!
我们要剪断绳子了 你现在在想什么？
We're about to cut the rope, what's going through your mind?
我只是在想我的兄弟 我的家人
I'm just thinking about my brothers, my family back home.
哇
Aw.
我为你加油
I'm cheering for you.
那么科尔比在想什么呢？
So what's going through your mind Colby?
你觉得你能撑多久?
How long do you think you'll hang?
没多久 我是较弱的一个 所以...
Not very long, I'm a weak one so...
无论如何你同意了 所以我们会剪的 他们都同意了 让大家知道
Well you agreed to it, so we'll do it. They both agreed to this, let it be known.
30个小时的时间归结于此
30-ish hours comes down to this.
杰克和马库斯要同时剪断双方的绳索 谁撑得时间最长谁就是赢家
Jake and Marcus are gonna cut the rope on both sides at the same time and whoever can hang the longest wins.
谁输了仍然会得到$1万美元 因为为啥不呢？（有钱任性）
Whoever loses will still get ten grand 'cause why not?
三 二 一 剪！
Three, two, one, cut!
-加油！科尔比 -来吧！
-Come on Colby! -Come on!
-你能赢的！
-You got this!
这可能等于$100万美元
This could equal a million dollars.
我的腿都动不了了
I can't even move my legs.
但是你刚赢了$1万美元
But you just won $10,000 though.
是的
Yeah.
这位就是我们的最终赢家！
And here is our winner!
他将在几周内继续争取$100万美元
He's going on to competefor one million dollars in a few weeks.
如果你想有机会和他竞争 一定要在照片墙上关注我或购买商品
If you want a chance to compete against him, make sure you follow me on Instagram or buy merch.
在未来的三个挑战中 所有的十二个人 将会是在照片墙上关注我或购买商品的人
Three more of these, all twelve people in the future three challenges, will be people that follow me on Instagram or buy merch.
你可以为$100万美元 和他们面对面竞争
You can face 'em, for one million dollars.
现在这是给我哥哥的
Now this was for my brother.
我想我们应该给他打电话
I think we should call him.
是的 让我们看看他要说什么
Yeah, let's see what he says.
-我想我们应该给他打电话 -猜猜你弟弟做了什么？
-I think we should call him. -Guess what your brother did?
天哪 请告诉我他赢了？
Oh my gosh, please tell me he won?
是的 他做到了 他取得了胜利
Yeah he did, he got the dub.
哦 我的天啊！
Oh my goodness!
我为你做的哥哥 因为我知道这对你意义重大
I did it for you, bro 'cause I know, this means a lot to you
我知道你希望你能站在这里
and I know you wish you could have been here.
所以我为你们坚持着
So I hung in there for you guys.
我知道这会让我们的生活变得更好 如果我能赢得那$100万
I know it's gonna make our lives a lot better if I can win that one mil.
我会为我们继续前进的 爱你
I'm gonna do it for us though. Love you.
我也要哭了 我的天哪
I'm crying now, ooh my goodness.
好的 几周后我们会再见
So we'll see you again in a few weeks, later guys.
另外 不要忘记我们仍在选择接下来三个“最后离开挑战”的视频的人
Also don't forget we're still selecting for the next three 'Last to Leave' videos.
如果你想参与竞争 请在照片墙上关注我或购买我的商品
If you want to compete, follow me on Instagram or buy my merch.
相信我 我很关心你们这些国际人士
Trust me guys, I care a lot about you international people
但是当你试图同时遵守美国和其他国家的法律时
but when trying to comply with the laws in America and other countries at the same time,
这就变得很难 很遗憾 这种抽奖选择只在美国进行
it's just hard, so sadly, this sweepstakes is only U.S. based.
另外快速补充 我们有一个大问题就是有人会冒充我
Also quick add in, we have a big problem with people impersonating me
我只会从我经过加V（verified）的MRBeast照片墙帐户向你发送消息
and I will only DM you from my verified Mr.Beast Instagram account.